# Elizabeth Hadik-Barkóczy

## **EXPERIENCE**

# Indeed, San Francisco — Software Engineering Intern

AUG 2022 – OCT 2022 – Cloud Security Engineering Team

Quickly gained knowledge of Indeed's deployments, both internal and cloud, as well as internal tooling APIs. Created design documentation and led meetings with the affected teams to earn the trust and buy-in from key stakeholders within Indeed's data governance team.

Specifically, delivered Indeed the capability to tag all its data stores in *AWS* with appropriate critical data tags where the source and destination lived in unrelated systems. This was achieved before the deadline by learning *Python*, *Boto3*, *Terraform* and *Jupiter1* within three weeks to write a cross-account Lambda function that stayed under a 3-second processing time.

JAN 2022 – AUG 2022 – Identity Platform Engineering Team

Another project was conducting data research to convince stake holders to update, rather than decommission the Passport Web App Account Lookup Tool.

Completely redesigned the User Interface by reaching out for user feedback, implemented UI data changes in *TypeScript/React*, and adjusted the *NodeJS/Express* API to perform optimized searches under 1 second.

## **Techtonica,** San Francisco — *Full-Stack Software Engineer Apprentice*

JUL 2021 – JAN 2022

Learned *Postgres, Express, React* and *NodeJS* (PERN) under strict deadlines at this project-based, collaborative training program, where 5 full-stack applications were developed and deployed. The capstone project, DaySlayer, utilized Auth0 for an authenticated web-based team management application and will be used by Techtonica for its program.

# **Soup Freaks,** San Francisco — *Technical + Marketing Manager* (Apps + Experiences)

FEB 2004 - APR 2013

Handled both the marketing and technical aspects for this food start-up and created a comprehensive and integrated system that managed and maintained the entire sales lifecycle: digital signage, in-store menus, self-service kiosks, and POS systems, resulting in an increase in brand awareness, 23% sales growth YOY, and an 85% customer retention rate.

Designed and developed a data supported website with ASP, resulting in effective product presentation, as well as a customized online ordering, management operational oversight and investor reporting tools.

# **EDUCATION**

CCSF, San Francisco — A.S. Computer Networking & Information Technology: Cybersecurity, Highest Honors (4.0 GPA).

May 2022

**CCSF,** San Francisco — *Advanced Certificate in Cyber Security, CNIT* May 2022

Amazon Web Services — *Cloud Practitioner Certification, AWS*May 2021 — Verify Certification Using This Link

# 415.505.2427

elizabeth@hadik-barkoczy.com

## **CAREER SUMMARY**

As a former Technical Manager of a software engineering consulting firm, I have experience with both software and hardware, delivering technical marketing demos for companies such as Intel, Microsoft, Seagate, Symantec and technology start-ups.

Passionate about technology, I have recently re-entered the software engineering world, focusing on Cybersecurity and learning the latest tech stacks for the field.

I desire to bring my unique combination of strategic vision, customer-service, focus on execution and updated technical skills to deliver tangible business results in a highly collaborative setting.

#### SKILLS

**Programming:** Python, Boto3, Terraform, Java, JavaScript, NodeJS, Typescript, HTML 5, and CSS

Cybersecurity Tools: AWS, AWS CWI, AWS IAM, AWS Lambda, Terraform, Boto 3, Snyk, Autopsy 4, Wireshark, Regedit, Cain and Abel, Metasploit, Nmap, CLI, Kali Linux, and Ubuntu

**Testing Tools:** JEST, and React Testing Library (RTL)

OS Platforms: MacOS (Unix), Linux, and Microsoft Windows

**Human Languages:** Hungarian, German, and Limited Spanish.

Cybersecurity Certifications:

Armis — Cyber Defense Core

December 2022

Verify Certification

Using This Link

FOUNDATIONAL





10/3/2022

Kristopher Katzenberger

Manager, Information Security

Indeed, Inc.

krisk@indeed.com

Re: Elizabeth Hadik-Barkoczy Recommendation

To Whom It May Concern,

I had the pleasure to meet Elizabeth Hadik-Barkoczy as part of the internship program we have within Indeed, Inc. She came to me after discovering her passion was combining Security and development work in order to achieve business objectives.

Elizabeth was with my team for 8 weeks and in that time she was able to fully understand the key deliverables that the team was needing help with but didn't have the time to tackle. Additionally, during that time, Elizabeth was able to quickly gain knowledge of our cloud deployments, and internal tooling APIs, and do the necessary cross-collaboration to gain trust and buy-in from key stakeholders within our data governance team. Specifically, Elizabeth delivered us the capability to tag all of our data stores in the cloud with appropriate critical data tags where the source and destination lived in unrelated systems. Elizabeth did this with minimal ramp-up time and a tight window in which to learn about and deliver a key initiative early.

I believe Elizabeth would be an excellent addition to any security team. Elizabeth has shown the ability to communicate effectively, understand and apply security concepts, and has impressed me personally with her ability to ramp up quickly within our complex environment. Your team will be gaining a rockstar.

	•			
Please teel tree	to reach out to	me at my email	ahove if you	have any questions.

Sincerely,

Kristopher Katzenberger